#### Contact

+917406823823 (Mobile) ritweek@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ritweek (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

C#

**ASP.NET MVC** 

Microsoft SQL Server

### Languages

C# (Professional Working)

English (Professional Working)

Hindi (Professional Working)

## Certifications

Human-Centered Design

Digital Acumen

Internet History, Technology, and Security

#### Honors-Awards

Distinguished Performer

# Ritweek Ranjan

Software Associate at PricewaterhouseCoopers - Service Delivery Center (PwC SDC)

Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

## Summary

I am a software engineer experienced in handling all problems and bugs using

C#,

.NET CORE1.0/2.0/3.1,

Azure Services,

Angular 5/6/8/9,

TypeScript,

ngrx/store,

ASP.Net with MVC,

WEB API,

Entity Framework,

SOL Server technologies,

Visual Studio and

Source control.

Excellent analytic, design and problem-solving abilities.

Extremely motivated and committed to delivering the highest Standard of work.

I am looking forward to utilizing my Knowledge, expertise, enhance my skills, abilities, and add value to your company.

# Experience

PricewaterhouseCoopers - Service Delivery Center (PwC SDC)
Software Associate
January 2019 - Present (1 year 7 months)
Bangalore

#### **TEKsystems**

2 years 1 month

Senior Developer April 2018 - December 2018 (9 months)

Bangalore, Karnataka, India

### Software Developer

December 2016 - April 2018 (1 year 5 months)

Bangalore, Karnataka, India

LogixHealth

Software Developer

May 2014 - July 2016 (2 years 3 months)

Bengaluru Area, India

Design, develop and modify Microsoft ASP.NET Applications, .NET components, Web Services, and Enterprise Services components.

Design, develop, and maintain SQL database schemas and scripts, including views, triggers and stored procedures.

Deploy .Net systems to various production and pre-production environments and troubleshoot issues.

Create technical documentation such as design documents, specifications, software architecture documents, and instructions.

Analyze design and architectural issues and questions.

Support and assist management of the project development team.

Work in a team environment using a structured development process and deliver applications on time and within budget.

Follow up with issues in an efficient manner, including working hand in hand with Quality Assurance, Project Management and/or Sr. Developers.

Regularly communicate project progress, issues, and risks to Project Manager.

Support existing applications.

Create and support complex code structures in both VB.NET and C#; Implement and support JQuery Code.

SkillAssure

Software Trainee

January 2014 - April 2014 (4 months)

Bengaluru Area, India

Application Support, Project Understanding, Bug and Change Request.

Technology: C#, SQL Server, MVC, WCF, Entity Framework.

Abhijeet Projects Ltd

**Electrical Engineer** 

March 2012 - December 2012 (10 months)

Chandwa, Jharkhand, India

BHEL make 270 X 4 MW); Review of all drawings/documents related to project.

Work execution as per schedule.

Testing and commissioning of E.O.T. and Miscellaneous cranes.

Erection, Testing & commissioning of electrical switchgears 33Kv, 6.6 Kv and 415 V.

Major role in our boiler hydro test for Phase-I from WTP end.

Allocation of construction power for our site's maintenance work.

Commissioning of LT & HT Switchgear along with preparation of some basic cable schedules for its safe completion.

Erection, Testing & Commissioning work of all LT and HT motors.

Erection, Testing & Commissioning work of all Dry type transformers of various ratings.

Maintained backups of all primary servers, PCs, and other hardware.

Hostage India
Event Co-ordinator
April 2011 - July 2011 (4 months)
Bangalore, India

Managing different corporate and stage shows.

Tenughat Thermal Power Station Ltd. (TTPS)
Summer Training
August 2009 - September 2009 (2 months)

Successfully completed a vocational training involving visits to several departments

of the plant like C&I, CHP, boiler area, switch yard, control room, T/G hall etc.

Interacted with key personnel to understand the process of thermal power generation.

## Education

Don Bosco Institute of Technology, BANGALORE Bachelor of Engineering (B.E.), Electrical and Electronics Engineering · (2007 - 2011)

Atomic Energy Central School 12TH, PCM-COM · (2002 - 2006)

# Activity

06/25/2020, Ritweek Ranjan added candidate to Senior Software Engineer